Sanjeev Bhasin welcomes the year, which looks cut off,
hello, tell me like a machine,
where is the attention and trend, wicket style boys, so I
think that writing actress is on the
table, if not today then tomorrow we will cross 15909
and comment, it means extremely good,
pick up the data, macro data is gold,
corporate results, you have seen it from
bank HDFC Bank, welcome to the
best profit saver on the 17382 and today I will give you it's
large cap, so in the last step,
now I will just do it
in Reliance HDFC Bank, today I will give
you news that Maruti has deepened 18,000
crores in the next five years and will invest
10 lakh vehicles and he himself in laughter Vijay on
you, the meeting multiple send food to homes,
overhead tank fiber multiple
Maruti is a weapon running plant, so first
introduce me, unquestionably Maruti 73,
take vacancy vision ₹100, if you want to
sell them in the next year, then you can imagine
vision 7373, take
Maruti stop loss of 10  71981 70610 Second
brother, he is high on
Jhalawar, I am very bullish on record to
sanction go to record, Sebi & General
Insurance World Mobile at 1540 42,
take stoploss at 1505, target more than 90,
give a plate, if it does not move today, but in the
second, your midcap banks will definitely move, you
just do it, you are already seeing a change in Bandhan Bank, Aryan and IDFC
First One Max,
you have three targets of 14 15 to 11 325,
of which it will move to 345, Indore Mandsaur district, this
Bandhan, RBL Bank, IDFC year and 22
midcap IT will be the best performer in the
SE internship TDS, let's see a
good momentum coming in winters, you
can see it, Singh saheb, many thanks to you,
good momentum in Maruti, ICICI
Lombard and just as you can see
Bandhan Bank, RBL Bank and IDBI
giving trends on IDFC Fan,
Nifty is 15, so
in a few minutes on your screen  Coming to where GO
is, J letter G and there is one more thing,
one thing worth noting here is that the
green of Bank Nifty on June 4, the email from where the
reversal happened,